mammahealth.com 2019-04-23

# Privacy Policy - Mamma Health

The following Privacy Policy governs the online information collection practices of mammahealth.com, referred to as “us” or “we” in this policy statement.

This Privacy Policy outlines the types of information that we gather about you while you are using any of our website(s), and the ways in which we may use this information.

Your privacy is very important to us and we are committed to respecting the privacy of the visitors to all of our sites. We are very careful with what we do with your information.

This Privacy Policy does not apply to any and all information you may provide to us or that we may collect apart from our sites (mail, telephone, social media, live events, webinars, and during program participation).

Read this Privacy Policy carefully, as well as the posted Terms and Conditions and Disclaimer before using this website. This Privacy Policy will be noted on all of the above websites listed.

By visiting and using any of the above websites, you agree that your use of the site is governed by this Privacy Policy. We reserve the right to update the effective date of the policy to reflect the date of any changes. By continuing to use any of the above sites after we post updated changes (reflected by the noted date) you accept the Privacy Policy as modified.

SECTION 1 – HOW WE COLLECT AND WHAT WE DO WITH YOUR INFORMATION

When you access or purchase something from our store:

When you purchase something from our store, as part of the buying and selling process, we collect the personal information you give us such as your name, address, email address or telephone number.

When you browse our store, we also automatically receive your computer’s internet protocol (IP) address in order to provide us with information that helps us learn about your browser and operating system. Our store also may use a standard feature found in browser software called a “cookie” to enhance your experience with the site. Our cookies do not collect personal, confidential information and are not spyware. A list of cookies used by our store is noted below. Cookies prevent you from having to re-enter your preferences on certain areas of the site where you may have entered preference information previously. You may set your internet web browser to refuse cookies or to remove cookies from your hard drive.

Email marketing (if applicable): With your permission, we may send you emails about our store, new products and other updates.

When you visit one of our websites:

We may collect and store personal or other information that you voluntarily supply to us online while you are visiting one of our websites and you “opt in” to receive our newsletters, blogs, emails and promotional communications.

We only contact individuals who specifically request that we do so or who have signed up to receive our messaging, purchased one of our products or programs, attended one of our programs or events or who have responded to a promotional campaign. The information we use is provided to us by you.

We use the information we collect from you while you are using our sites in a variety of ways, including using the information to customize features; advertising that appear on the sites; and making other offers available to you via email, direct mail or otherwise.

Information we may collect from social networking sites:

If you choose to log into our services through Facebook Connect, we will request your permission to collect the following information about you: your e-mail address, name, profile picture, cover photo, friends, gender, networks (e.g., school), age range, language, country, and other information that you have chosen to make public. We may append this information to other information that we collect about you. If you “like” us on Facebook, we also may collect your email address. We may also post to your Facebook wall.

We may also provide your information to third parties, such as service providers.

SECTION 2 – THIRD-PARTY SERVICES

We do not sell your personal information to third parties.

In general, the third-party providers used by us will only collect, use and disclose your information to the extent necessary to allow them to perform the services they provide to us.

However, certain third-party service providers, such as payment gateways and other payment transaction processors, have their own privacy policies in respect to the information we are required to provide to them for your purchase-related transactions. For these providers, we recommend that you read their privacy policies so you can understand the manner in which your personal information will be handled by these providers.

In particular, remember that certain providers may be located in or have facilities that are located a different jurisdiction than either you or us. So if you elect to proceed with a transaction that involves the services of a third-party service provider, then your information may become subject to the laws of the jurisdiction(s) in which that service provider or its facilities are located.

Once you leave our store, or are redirected to a third-party website or application, you are no longer governed by this Privacy Policy or our website’s Terms of Service.

Links

When you click on links on our store or websites, they may direct you away from our site. We are not responsible for the privacy practices of other sites and encourage you to read their privacy statements.

Partners

We may make some content, products and services available through our site by emailing messages to you through cooperative relationships with third-party provider partners. We may share with our provider partner any information you provide, or that is collected, in the course of visiting any pages our sites. In comes cases, the provider partner may collect information from you directly, in which cases the privacy policy of our provider partner may apply to the provider partner’s use of your information.

Google Analytics

We may use third-party service providers, such as Google Analytics, to evaluate the use of our Website. Such third party service providers use automated devices and applications to evaluate use of our Websites and services. We or our service providers use these tools to help us improve our Websites, performance, and user experiences. These entities may use cookies and other tracking technologies, such as web beacons or Flash LSO, to perform their services.

SECTION 3 – CONSENT

By visiting and using any of the above sites, you agree that your use of the site is governed by this Privacy Policy. We reserve the right to update the effective date of the policy to reflect the date of any changes. By continuing to use any of the above sites after we post updated changes (reflected by the noted date) you accept the Privacy Policy as modified.

When you provide us with personal information to complete a transaction, verify your credit card, place an order, arrange for a delivery or return a purchase, we imply that you consent to our collecting it and using it for that specific reason only.

If we ask for your personal information for a secondary reason, like marketing, we will either ask you directly for your expressed consent, or provide you with an opportunity to say no.

Please keep in mind that whenever you voluntarily make your personal information available for viewing by third parties online – for example, on message boards, web logs, through email, or in chat areas, that information can be seen, collected and used by others besides us. We cannot be responsible for any unauthorized third-party use of such information.

How do I withdraw my consent?

Your information related to visiting our sites is stored at the list server that delivers our content and messaging. Your information can only be accessed by those who help manage those lists in order to deliver email to those who would like to receive it.

All of the messaging or emails that we send to you include an unsubscribe link in them. You can remove yourself at any time from our mailing list by clicking on the unsubscribe link.

If after you opt-in, you change your mind, you may withdraw your consent for us to contact you, for the continued collection, use or disclosure of your information, at any time, by [contacting us](https://mammahealth.com/contact/).

SECTION 4 – DISCLOSURE

We may disclose your personal information if we are required by law to do so or if you violate our Terms of Service.

Please also note that as our business grows, we may buy or sell various assets. In the unlikely event that we sell some or all of our assets; or one or more of our websites is acquired by another company, information about our users may be among the transferred assets.

SECTION 5 – OUR STORE

Our store is hosted on Shopify Inc. They provide us with the online e-commerce platform that allows us to sell our products and services to you.

Your data is stored through Shopify’s data storage, databases and the general Shopify application. They store your data on a secure server behind a firewall.

Payment/Purchase Transaction Information:

If you choose a direct payment gateway to complete your purchase, then Shopify stores your credit card data. It is encrypted through the Payment Card Industry Data Security Standard (PCI-DSS). Your purchase transaction data is stored only as long as is necessary to complete your purchase transaction. After that is complete, your purchase transaction information is deleted.

All direct payment gateways adhere to the standards set by PCI-DSS as managed by the PCI Security Standards Council, which is a joint effort of brands like Visa, MasterCard, American Express and Discover.

PCI-DSS requirements help ensure the secure handling of credit card information by our store and its service providers.

For more insight, you may also want to read Shopify’s Terms of Service (https://www.shopify.com/legal/terms) or Privacy Statement (https://www.shopify.com/legal/privacy).

SECTION 6 – OUR STORE’S SECURITY

To protect your personal information, our store via Shopify, Inc. takes reasonable precautions and follows industry best practices to make sure your information is not inappropriately lost, misused, accessed, disclosed, altered or destroyed.

If you provide us with your credit card information, the information is encrypted using secure socket layer technology (SSL) and stored with an AES-256 encryption. Although no method of transmission over the Internet or electronic storage is 100% secure, we follow all PCI-DSS requirements and implement additional generally accepted industry standards.

SECTION 7 – OUR STORE’S USE OF COOKIES

Here is a list of cookies that we use in our store. We’ve listed them here so you that you can choose if you want to opt-out of cookies or not.

_session_id, unique token, sessional, Allows Shopify to store information about your session (referrer, landing page, etc.).

_shopify_visit, no data held, Persistent for 30 minutes from the last visit, Used by our website provider’s internal stats tracker to record the number of visits

_shopify_uniq, no data held, expires midnight (relative to the visitor) of the next day, Counts the number of visits to a store by a single customer.

cart, unique token, persistent for 2 weeks, Stores information about the contents of your cart.

_secure_session_id, unique token, sessional

storefront_digest, unique token, indefinite If the shop has a password, this is used to determine if the current visitor has access.

SECTION 8 – AGE OF CONSENT

This site is not directed to children under the age of 18 and we do NOT knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under the age of 18 as part of any of our sites. If we become aware that we have inadvertently received personally identifiable information from a user under the age of 18, we will delete such information from our records. It is not our intention of offer any of our products, programs or services to minors.

SECTION 9 – CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY

We reserve the right to modify this privacy policy at any time, so please review it frequently. Changes and clarifications will take effect immediately upon their posting on the website. If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you here that it has been updated, so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we use and/or disclose it.

QUESTIONS AND CONTACT INFORMATION

If you would like to: access, correct, amend or delete any personal information we have about you, register a complaint, or simply want more information [contact](https://mammahealth.com/contact/) our Privacy Compliance Officer.
